What's going on?
怎么了?
What do you mean?
什么怎么了?
I'm your brother.
我是你的弟弟
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
如果有什么 你可以和我说说
It's all right, really.
没事的 真的
Okay.
好吧
One more chapter and we'll take a break.
再修改一章 我们就休息
David !
大卫
Get help!
快叫医生!
Whoever did this, I want them dead or in custody
无论是谁干的 在俄国人到来之前
by the time the Russians get here.
我要他死或者进监狱
I would ask that you consider postponing the signing of the treaty, Sir.
我请求您推迟签署协定
No.
不
Absolutely not.
绝对不行
I think...
我认为...
that David was killed because of
大卫被杀是因为一些
something he was about to tell me.
他本想告诉我的事情
He said that it concerned national security
他说关系到国家安全
and that it involved you.
并且也牵涉到你
Was she all right?
她还好吧?
No, Walt, she's not all right.
不 沃尔特 她不好
She's having another one of her delusions.
她又产生了另外一个幻觉
What is this, an interrogation?
你在干什么 审犯人?
I just don't like being lied to.
我只是不想被欺骗
No one's lying to you, Derek.
没有人在骗你 德里克
Yeah, I'm not hungry.
我不饿
Sorry.
抱歉
You don't owe me an explanation.
你不需要向我解释
If you had wanted to tell me about your past
我清楚如果你想告诉我你过去
you would have told me already.
的事情的话你早就说了
Yeah?
喂?
Jack, I know this isn't protocol,
杰克 我知道这违反规定
please don't hang up on me, I need your help.
请不要挂断 我需要你的帮助
They got Tony and Michelle,
他们对托尼和米歇尔下手了
Michelle is dead, Tony's in critical condition,
米歇尔死了托尼还没有脱离危险期
now they're gonna kill me.
现在他们又要来杀我了
What the hell are you doing here?
你到这里来干什么?
I'm sorry I followed you, I'm just...
很抱歉我跟踪了你我只是...
I'm just worried about my mother.
我只是担心我妈妈
You're going with me.
你必须和我走
Hold your fire, Chloe!
停火 科洛伊
Palmer was the primary target.
帕默是我的首要目标
Set you up. Make it looks like you did it.
来陷害你让别人认为都是你做的
You're the one that killed Palmer.
你就是杀害帕默的凶手
Yeah.
是的
The following takes place between 8Am and 9Am.
以下是发生于上午8点至9点之间的故事
The President's retreat is still vulnerable.
戴维营守备的还是不够牢靠
You need to post 2 more people here at Delta.
你需要在这里再增派几个人手
It's a high probability point of infiltration.
这里很有可能被侵入
We'll have to pull assets from somewhere else.
我们只能从别的地方调人手了
Yeah, Marcie, hi.
玛茜 你好
Can you give me the figures?
能告诉我确切的数字么?
Excuse me, Sir. Sorry to interrupt.
对不起 先生 抱歉打扰
What is it, Edgar?
什么事 埃德加?
We have a visual on a suspect, I thought you might want to know.
我们找到了一个嫌疑犯的图像就来通知您了
He may be the Palmer shooter.
帕默总统可能就是被他杀害的
Were you able to make an ID?
能确定他的身份么?
I think you should see for yourself.
我想您还是亲自看一下吧
About an hour before President Palmer was shot...
在帕默总统遇刺前一小时
someone broke into the service entrance of the building across the street,
有人穿过街道闯入狙击手射击
the one the sniper used.
的那栋大厦
We have a frame grab from a security video.
我们截取了一段监控录像
I ran it through a high-res filter,
经过高精度过滤器
so it may take a few seconds to render.
可能需要几秒钟的时间渲染
Audrey.
奥黛丽
What is going on here, Jack?
这到底是怎么回事  杰克?
They're setting me up to take the fall
他们想让我当替死鬼
for Palmer's assassination.
说我刺杀了帕默总统
Palmer's not even president anymore.
帕默已经不是总统的
Why would they want him dead?
他们为什么还要置他于死地呢?
I don't know.
不知道
You need to get as far away from here as you can.
你必须走得越远越好
Just disappear.
最好消失
No, what I need to do is to find out who really killed President Palmer.
不  我要找出是谁要杀死帕默总统
How are you gonna do that?
你想怎么做?
Start at the beginning.
首先
Investigate the original crime scene.
从遇害的第一现场开始
David Palmer was visiting his brother when he was shot.
大卫・帕默遇害时正和他弟弟在一起
Maybe he left something there that can help me.
或许他能帮我
That's crazy.
不行的
Palmer was assassinated an hour ago.
总统一小时前遇刺
The place is gonna be crawling with Secret Service,
那里肯定聚集了许多特工
FBI, local police.
联邦调查局  当地警察
I need access to a building schematic
我需要权限来得到建筑示意图
and an interagency deployment grid.
和联合行动任务安排表
Can you get that for me or not?
能帮我弄到么?
Yeah.
可以的
I should be able to log on remotely from the site.
只要我能从远程登陆
Okay. Come on,
好的
let's go.
我们走
How could you kill that guy?
你怎么能杀他?
I'm sorry you had to see that
很抱歉让你看到这个
Derek. Get in the van.
德里克 快上车
I'm not going anywhere with you.
我哪儿也不跟你去
You're gonna do exactly what I tell you
你必须按我说的做
until I pass you off to your mother.
直到我把你交给你妈妈
Let go of me.
放开我
Let's get something straight, kid.
和你直说吧 孩子
The only reason you're still conscious is because
你之所以现在还活着
I don't want to carry you.
我因为我不想拖累你
Now get in the van.
现在赶紧给我上车
Preliminary analysis indicates the video hasn't been doctored.
初步分析显示录像没有被修改过的痕迹
Then Jack was in the building the sniper fired from
这么说在狙击手杀害帕默总统时
at the same time President Palmer was assassinated.
杰克也在那栋建筑里
That's impossible.
这不可能
This whole thing is impossible.
整件事都不可能
Bill, you were there when Jack was shot.
比尔  杰克死时你也在场
He had not pulse, no vitals.
没有脉搏  没有心跳
And I have no idea how Jack staged his own death.
杰克的死是如何上演的我全然不知
But I understand his reasons.
但我理解他的处境
He was about to be handed over to the Chinese government
他即将被移交给中国政府
to spend the rest of his life in prison.
并在监狱中度过余生
None of that explains why Jack would want to kill David Palmer.
这跟杰克要杀害帕默总统又有什么关系呢
I had Curtis pull the phone logs.
我让柯蒂斯查过电话记录
Palmer, Tony and Michelle were all talking to Jack
帕默 托尼米还有米歇尔
right before he was supposedly killed.
在杰克"死"后都一直和他保持着电话联系
Our working theory is that
我们认为他们合谋
they conspired to help Jack fake his own death.
制造了杰克死亡的假相
Now you're saying that Jack was behind the attack
那么你认为是杰克策划了总统的暗杀
on Tony and Michelle, too?
并且托尼和米歇尔也是他杀的  对吗?
Why would Jack want to kill the people who helped him?
杰克为什么要杀害曾经帮助过他的人呢?
Something may have happened and he stopped
发生了某些事情使杰克
trusting them to keep his secret.
不再相信他们能替他保守秘密
Jack would never murder his friends.
杰克永远不会杀害他的朋友
Audrey...
奥黛丽
I don't want to believe Jack did this, either.
我也不相信这是杰克干的
But right now,
但是现在
it's the best explanation
只能这样认为了
for the evidence that we have.
就手头的证据来看只有这种可能了
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
The White House needs to know about this.
白宫有必要知道此事
Yeah, I'll call the President.
是的  我这就给总统打电话
Bill.
比尔
What is it, Curtis?
什么事  柯蒂斯?
I had Adamson run a data recovery operation
我曾让亚当森对托尼
on Tony's phone records.
的电话记录进行恢复
They show Chloe was on those calls
他们说克洛伊也在那些电话之中
with President Palmer and Tony.
包括帕默总统和托尼
Chloe knew Jack was alive?
克洛伊知道杰克还活着?
Apparently.
显然是
We called her in an hour ago, she should have been here by now.
一小时前通知过她现在应该在这里了
I've been trying to call her on her cell but she's not answering.
我一直在打她的手机但她不接
I wanted to run a locate but Spencer talked me out of it.
我想利用卫星定位但斯宾塞不让我管
- If anything happens to her... - Stop !
- 克洛伊要是有个好歹 都是你的错  - 打住
Have Adamson track her cell,
让亚当森追踪她手机
we need to get to her before Jack does.
我们要在杰克之前找到她
Put out an interagency alert.
发布紧急通告
Jack Bauer is now the prime suspect
杰克・鲍尔 是首要嫌疑犯
in President Palmer's assassination.
参与了帕默总统的暗杀
Emphasize that he's a former agent,
特别指出他曾是特工
well-trained and should be considered extremely dangerous.
训练有素并且极度危险
Excuse me, Sir.
打扰一下  先生
What is it Walt ?
什么事 沃尔特?
Mrs. Logan called again.
洛根夫人又打电话过来
I can't keep putting her off
我无法阻止她和
about this phone call with David Palmer.
大卫・帕默通话
Why would David Palmer call my wife
大卫・帕默为什么要打给我的夫人
about a national security threat?
说一些关于国家安全的问题?
That's what she says he wanted to talk to her about.
她就是这么说的
A matter of national security.
和国家安全有关
Maybe if I investigated the phone call?
或许我应该调查一下来电?
No, you need to stay focused on the Summit.
不 你还是关注一下高峰会吧
I am, Sir, which is why we can't risk having
是的先生  这也是为什么我们不能冒险
Mrs. Logan obsess about this phone call.
让洛根夫人被这种电话所影响
Showing her the truth might help her
把真相告诉她
get on with her responsibilities today.
或许能让她重新担当起她的责任
So what are you... what are you suggesting?
你说怎么办?
Well, if David Palmer called her yesterday,
如果大卫・帕默昨天真的给她打过电话
our communications office will have a recording of their conversation.
我们的信息处应该还留有记录
Get that for me.
帮我找出来
Yes, Sir.
遵命
And Walt...
沃尔特
thank you for doing this.
谢谢你所做的
Mr. President, Audrey Raines is holding on line 3.
总统先生  奥黛丽・瑞恩斯在3号线
Ms. Raines, this is President Logan.
瑞恩斯小姐  我是洛根总统
You're also on with Walt Cummings.
还有沃尔特・卡明斯
Sir, CTU has a suspect in the
先生 CTU发现一名
assassination of President Palmer.
暗杀帕默总统的嫌疑犯
Good!
好!
Who is it?
是谁?
Ms. Raines?
瑞恩斯小姐?
It's Jack Bauer, Sir.
是杰克・鲍尔
Jack Bauer's dead.
杰克・鲍尔已经死了
We've all been living under that assumption, Sir.
看来您还和我一样被蒙在鼓里
I don't understand.
我不明白
What makes you think it's Bauer?
是什么让你们认为是鲍尔干的?
CTU has verified surveillance video
CTU已经核实了监控录像
placing Jack Bauer at the same time,
杰克・鲍尔和狙击手在同一时间
in the same building as the
出现在同一地点
sniper who killed President Palmer.
正是帕默总统遇刺的时候
Audrey, this is Walt Cummings.
奥黛丽  我是沃尔特・卡明斯
Let me get clear on this.
我想确认一下
Are you saying that Bauer shot David Palmer?
你说是杰克・鲍尔杀害了大卫・帕默?
We're proceeding under that assumption, yes.
现在的行动都是以这个假设为前提的  是的
Why? For what possible reason?
为什么?他这样做是为了什么?
David Palmer might have known that
大卫・帕默可能知道
Jack Bauer was alive,
杰克・鲍尔 还活着
knowledge that he shared with three other CTU agents,
同时知道此事的还有CTU其他三名特工
all of whom have been targeted in the last hour.
他们在过去的一小时内都受到了攻击
The man does have a history of insubordination,
曾有记录显示此人有违抗命令
irrational behavior, drug addiction.
行为反常及吸毒史
Jack Bauer has a history of great service to this country.
杰克・鲍尔曾经是这个国家最好的卫士
How does this affect your threat assessment for the Summit?
你认为这会对这次会见产生影响?
We're still recommending that you delay or reschedule
我们仍然建议您推迟或重新安排会见时间
until Jack Bauer's apprehended.
直到杰克・鲍尔被控制为止
Ms. Raines, you have a suspect. Find him.
瑞恩斯小姐  既然值得怀疑 找到他
Yes, Sir.
遵命
Sir, President Suvarov arrives within the hour.
先生  苏沃洛夫总统一小时内就要到了
Should we think about informing his security chief
我们是否要通知他的安全部长
that he's a potential target?
告知其可能的危险?
No. No.
不
I want this information limited to those involved
我想把消息封锁在
in the manhunt for Jack Bauer. Understood?
那些搜索杰克・鲍尔的人中 明白?
Yes, Sir.
明白
I found Haas.
找到哈斯了
He and his men are all dead.
他和手下都死了
How did this happen?
怎么回事?
I'm not sure.
不清楚
The last time I spoke to Haas
最后一次和他谈话他说要去
he was about to move on Bauer and the woman.
抓鲍尔和那女人
Is there any sign of Bauer now?
有鲍尔的踪影么?
No.
没有
I'll dispatch a team and track him.
我会再派队人跟踪他的
We'll have him in 24 hours.
24小时内将他解决
No, let CTU find Bauer.
不  让CTU去找鲍尔
Once they have him in custody, we'll take him out.
等他们将他逮捕后  咱们再把她带出来
You're not concerned Bauer will impede the operation?
你不怕鲍尔阻止咱们的行动么?
He won't have chance.
他不会的
We launch in less than an hour.
一小时内我们的行动就开始
All of their hardware's military spec.
所有的装备都是军用的
Fragmentation grenades, percussion grenades...
破片手榴弹 定向爆破手榴弹
Here's a comm unit we can use.
这里有个我们可以利用的通讯设备
Who are these people?
他们都是些什么人?
Yeah?
是我?
Frank, will you please tell me what's going on?
弗兰克  能告诉我究竟发生了什么事么?
Diane, I know it's hard, but please try not to worry.
黛安  我知道你暂时无法接受但请你不必担心
Derek is fine.
德里克没事
Where are you now?
你现在在哪儿?
I'm about a half hour outside of L.A.
到洛杉矶还有半小时
Just tell me where to meet you.
到哪儿去找你
I don't know yet.
还不知道
Just keep heading towards the city.
一直朝市区开
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
我会尽快给你消息的
Can I talk to him?
可以和他通话么?
Of course, yeah.
当然  稍等
It's your mother. Talk to her.
是你妈妈  和她说吧
Mom?
妈?
Derek, are you okay?
德里克  你还好么?
Yeah, I'm all right.
是的  我没事
Are you sure?
真的?
Jack, we're about a block away.
杰克  还有一个街区就到了
Say good-bye to your mother.
和妈妈说再见吧
I have to hang up now, Mom.
我必须挂了  妈妈
Don't worry I am fine.
别担心 我很好
Derek, I love you.
德里克  我爱你
Me, too.
我也爱你
Give me the phone.
把电话给我
Get to the back of the vehicle.
到里面去
Go!
快点!
While security agencies are remaining hushed,
在安全机关还保持沉默的同时
speculation begins to grow.
各种猜测连续不断
We're told, though, that that speculation
我们被告知
will not be addressed
不能公开这些猜测
because the government says security right now
因为政府说时下的安全被视为
is of utmost importance.
是最重要的
Now, look behind me,
在我身后
you'll see the Los Angeles apartment building
你会看到洛杉矶政府大楼
where President David Palmer was assassinated
大卫・帕默总统
a little more than an hour ago.
一小时前就是在这里遇刺身亡的
You can also see Americans
你还可以看到许多的美国人
of all ages have started to gather
包括各年龄的人都聚集在了这里
to mourn and pay their last respects
一同来悼念他们那
to the beloved former president,
受人尊敬的前总统
All right, go on through.
好了  可以走了
Let her through.
让她过去
We're clear.
没人了
Come on up front.
到前面来
Hold the light on the bag.
照着袋子
Can you get a wireless access point from down here?
在这能找到无线接入点么?
Yeah, I'm reading the agents' transponders.
是的  我正在读取特勤人员的步话机信号
I can track their locations to within three feet.
可以追踪到他们三英尺内的位置
Jack! There are 167 agents in and around the location,
杰克  这里共有167名特勤人员
25 of them in Wayne Palmer's apartment alone.
其中的25个分散在韦恩・帕默的房间
I know...
知道了
that's why we better hope that this is gonna be
所以我们最好希望
the last place they're gonna be looking for me.
他们没有想到我会在这里
Testing 1, 2, testing 1, 2, 3.
测试 1 2 测试 1 2 3
Okay.
好了
This is field ops communication unit.
这是一个区域行动通信单元
All you need to do is put it in your ear and we're set to go.
你只要把他放在耳朵里然后稍加设定
Derek, put out the light.
德里克  把手电筒关掉
Officer.
那个谁谁
All right, let me check that.
稍等 我帮你查一下
What...
怎么回事
Relax.
放心
He's really good at this.
他这方面很在行的
You sure he's okay?
他不会有事吧?
Yeah.
不会
I think.
我想是的
Chloe, do you copy?
克洛伊能听到么?
Yeah.
能
Wayne Palmer's apartment is the penthouse.
韦恩・帕默的房间在顶楼套房
Going up now.
我这就上去
Jack, there are four agents waiting at the lobby.
杰克  大厅里有四个
Hold off on going up if you can.
不能再往上走了
Too late.
来不及了
I'm entering the apartment.
我到了
Most of the agents are in the living room.
大部分的人都在客厅
That must be where Palmer was shot.
帕默很可能就是在那儿遇害的
There are two rooms to the north,
北面有两个房间
15 feet probably bedrooms...
15英尺  很可能是卧室
they're clear, no agents.
那里没有特勤人员
This first room is a study.
第一间是书房
Let me know if anyone comes this way.
有人来的话通知我
Will do, Jack.
好的  杰克
You keep calling him Jack.
你一直叫他杰克
He told my mother and I his name's Frank.
他告诉我和妈妈  他叫弗兰克
Who is he, really?
他到底是谁?
His name's Jack Bauer.
他叫杰克・鲍尔
Up until a year and a half ago
直到一年半以前
he worked for the government.
他曾为政府工作
Is that why we're in the building
这就是为什么我们
where the president was killed?
来到总统遇害的大楼么?
Please don't ask me any more questions.
请不要再问我了
Can't you at least tell me
能不能至少告诉我
why he had to pretend he was someone else?
他为什么要装成别人?
Certain people thought the best way to cover up their mistakes
有人认为掩盖自己错误的最好办法
was to get rid of Jack.
就是除掉杰克
You mean, kill him?
你是说 杀了他?
Yes.
没错
Jack had to give up everything and everyone in his life,
杰克不得不放弃他生活中的全部
including his daughter.
包括他的女儿
He has a daughter?
他还有女儿?
I've already told you more than I should.
我告诉你的已经够多了
I have the computer in the study booted up.
我打开了一台书房里的电脑
President Palmer had a user account.
帕默总统有个帐户
Is it password-secured?
有密码保护么?
No.
没有
There are about a dozen files.
这里有一打的文件
Only one of them's encrypted.
但只有一个是加密的
That's where I'm gonna look.
正是我要看的那个
Okay, give me the computer's IP address.
好的  告诉我你的IP地址
I'll upload a decryption program to it.
我上传一个解密程序给你
Hold on.
稍等
292.162.12.2
292.162.12.2
Someone's at the door.
门口有人
Not according to the deployment grid.
部署表格里看不到
There are no agents there.
那里没有人
Do not move. Do not raise your voice.
不许动   不要出声
You son of a bitch.
你这个婊子养的
You killed my brother.
你杀死了我哥哥
Mr. Palmer, you know I didn't do that.
帕默先生  你知道那不是我干的
Whatever evidence they showed you
无论他们有什么证据
against me has been fabricated.
你知道那都是伪造的
I served your brother for years.
我为你哥哥工作多年
I would've gladly given my life for his.
即使牺牲性命也在所不辞
He was my friend.
他是我的朋友
The only reason that I am here,
我来这里唯一的目的
is to try and figure out why and how he was assassinated.
就是要找出他是为什么并且怎样被暗害的
I was hoping to find clues on that computer.
我希望能在那台电脑上找到答案
Why don't you step into the next room, Jack,
你为什么不换个房间  杰克
and ask the Secret Service to help you find it?
向那些特勤人员寻求帮助?
Because I'm being set up.
因为我是被陷害的
Whoever's behind this has planted evidence against me
策划这事的人就是要陷害我
making me the shooter.
让我成为凶手
It would be useless to try and convince the authorities otherwise.
我说什么别人都不会相信的
You think you're gonna convince me?
那你认为我会信服么?
If I killed your brother,
如果我杀害了你哥哥
why didn't I kill you
为什么不杀了你
when you walked through the door?
就在你进来的那一刹那?
Think about this, Wayne.
想想吧韦恩
Why would I be here?
我来这是为了什么?
Please... I need your help.
我需要你的帮助
Jack, how do you expect me to
杰克 在这种情况下
believe you under these circumstances?
你要我怎么相信你?
Take the gun.
拿着枪
Jack, what are you doing?
杰克 你在干什么?
...that after two terms in the House
曾两次入住白宫
and one in the Senate,
并且一次进入议院
David Palmer was elected president with a 60% plurality.
帕默总统以60％的支持率赢得大选
There you are, Mrs. Logan.
原来您在这儿  洛根夫人
David and I first got to know each other
大卫和我第一次相识
when he was elected to Congress.
是他入选议会的时候
He and Charles never saw eye to eye politically, but...
他和查尔斯在政治上一向合不来
David never let that get in the way of our friendship.
但大卫从未让此影响到我们之间的友谊
Oh... that picture's from his inauguration.
那是他的就职演说
At the ball
舞会上
I was one of the first people David asked to dance.
我是大卫第一个邀请跳舞的人
Mrs. Logan... I need a few more minutes with your hair...
洛根夫人 我需要几分钟来帮您梳头
I know! I can do it myself.
我知道! 我可以自己来!
Just trying to help.
我想帮忙而已
I'm sorry, Evelyn,
我很抱歉  伊夫林
I know. I'm sorry.
实在抱歉
Mrs. Logan...
洛根夫人
May I have a word?
能谈谈么?
Of course.
当然
The president asked me to look into the call
总统让我调查电话记录
from David Palmer that you... told him about.
关于您和大卫・帕默的
I was beginning to think you were ignoring me.
我认为你会不管不问
So when did this call take place?
通话大概是在什么时间?
Last night.
昨晚
It woke me up.
吵醒了我
I had fallen asleep watching the news,
我看着看着电视就睡着了
so it was somewhere between 10:00 and 11:00.
应该是在十点和十一点之间
Well, I'll have someone pull up the call from the audio archives.
好的  我这就找人去提取声音档案
Walt.
沃尔特
He doesn't believe me, does he?
他不相信我说的  对么?
Charles.
查尔斯
He thinks I'm making the whole thing up.
他认为这些都是我编造的
I wouldn't say that, Mrs. Logan.
我不这么认为  洛根夫人
Well, of course you wouldn't say it.
你当然不这么认为
-Mrs. Logan...
洛根夫人...
Walt, you can go now.
沃尔特  你可以走了
President David Palmer, dead today at age 55.
总统 大卫・帕默 享年55岁
Your brother say or do anything
你哥哥在遇害前
out of the ordinary before he was shot?
有没有反常的言语或行为?
He was acting distracted ever since he came to Los Angeles.
他一来到洛杉矶就显得心烦意乱
I finally called him on it this morning.
我今早与他见面
What'd he say?
他都说了些什么?
He never had the chance to say anything, Jack.
他没来得及说任何事  杰克
The decryption program's finished running.
解密程序运行完毕
You should be able to open the file.
文件应该可以打开了
Okay, I'm going into it now.
好的  我这就试试
That's the first chapter of his memoir.
是他回忆录的第一章
That doesn't make any sense...
这说不通
why would he encrypt that?
他为什么要加密这个?
I mean, there are printouts of it all over the place.
到处都有这个的打印版
Maybe he hid some information in the document.
或许他在文档中隐藏了某些信息
We're gonna have to compare this to the printout,
需要将这个和打印版对比
see if he added or changed anything.
看是否有改动
Got one right here.
这儿有一份
You haven't sent the file allocations.
你还没有将文件配置发送出去
- What's the problem? - I need a higher level access code.
- 到底是怎么回事?  - 我需要一个高级别的访问口令
Look, if you're still upset about me and Chloe...
你要还因为科洛依的事情心烦
I don't care about that.
我根本没放在心上
I care that if you hadn't left her on her own this morning,
要不是你今早的置之不理
maybe she'd be okay right now.
或许她现在已经没事了
Don't you think I know that?
我难道不这么想么?
Look, you're just making it harder for me to do my job.
你让我无法安心处理手上的工作
Use Chloe's access code: JJ72.
用科洛依的进入口令: JJ72.
You won't get fire-walled with it.
这个可以跳过防火墙
Thank you.
多谢
Edgar.
埃德加
What?
怎么了?
This is weird.
有点不对劲
I tried logging in under Chloe's access code...
我用科洛依的口令登陆
the system says I'm already signed in.
系统说帐号已经登陆了
Let me see...
我看一下...
That's because Chloe's logged in, remotely.
她确实登入服务器了 远程
Are you sure it's her?
你确定是她?
Yes... see the way the traffic's redirected through an external socket?
是的 因为数据是从外部端口进入的
Even I don't know how to do that.
连我不知道她是怎么做的
Then she's alive.
这么说她还活着
Buchanan.
布坎南
Sir, it's Edgar. I think we can find Chloe.
我是埃德加  我想我们找到科洛依了
How ?
怎么找到的?
She's accessing our system through a laptop.
她正使用笔记本远程登陆我们的系统
I'm running a locate now.
我这就去定位
What's she using our system to do?
她在用我们的系统干什么?
All I can see from here is she's tracking
我这里只能看出
Secret Service and FBI deployments.
她在跟踪特勤和联邦人员
The locate came back.
找到了
She's at Wayne Palmer's building.
她在韦恩・帕默的楼里
The signal's faint.
信号很弱
It's possible she's in the parking garage under the building.
很可能是在地下停车场
Let me know if she changes location.
她变换地点时通知我
Why would Chloe be at the scene of
科洛依为什么要在
Palmer's assassination, tracking agents?
帕默遇害的现场跟踪特勤人员?
She wouldn't be...
她是不会...
unless someone was forcing her.
除非有别人逼着她做
What do you mean?
你在说什么?
Maybe Jack left evidence behind he needs to erase.
或许杰克在消除遗留下的证据
Surrounded by all of those agents?
当着那么多的特勤人员?
Bill, that doesn't make sense.
比尔 这不可能
Jack can explain it to us when we apprehend him.
当我们抓住杰克时他会向我们解释的
This is Bill Buchanan at CTU. I need to speak
我是CTU的比尔・布坎南
to the Secret Service field director immediately.
马上叫你们特工局的头头听电话
Yes.
喂?
Have you left yet?
离开了么?
No, we were delayed.
没有  我们被耽误了
We're still loading the truck.
还在装车
You should be on your way by now.
你现在应该在路上了
Be there in 20 minutes, as planned.
20分钟之内赶到  计划不变
Call me when you're approaching.
到了给我打电话
Wait, stop, stop, stop, stop...
等 停 停 停 停...
Right there
那儿
he added something in the middle of a sentence:
他在句子中间加了什么东西
a name and an address.
一个姓名和地址
There.
在这儿
"Chevensky - 16 Transport Way."
"切文斯基 运送路16号"
Chloe, did you get that? It looks like an address.
克洛伊 你看到了么? 看起来像个地址
Yes.
是的
Transport Way is a street at the Ontario airport.
运送路是安大略机场一条街道的名字
Okay, I want you to check all inbound flights into Ontario.
好  你查一下安大略所有将要降落的航班
Look for a passenger Chevensky. Try and make the connection.
查找一位名叫切文斯基的乘客想办法与他取得联系
Jack, the Secret Service is changing its deployment.
杰克  特工局正在改变他们的部署
How?
怎么回事?
Suddenly, there are a lot of agents moving into the building.
突然间有很多的特工进入大楼
I'm on my way down.
我这就下来
They know that I'm here.
他们知道我在这儿
Let me help you get out of here, Jack.
我帮你离开这儿  杰克
No.
不
You can't risk being connected to me.
你不能冒这个险
And until we know who to trust,
除非找到我们可信赖的人
you can't tell anybody about what we found, do you understand?
你不能把我们找到的告诉任何人 明白?
I'm going to do everything I can
我会尽我所能
to find out who did this to your brother.
来找出杀害你哥哥的真凶的
I'll be in touch.
我会联系你的
Chloe, I need another way out of here.
克洛伊  我需要另外一条路线离开这里
Checking.
查找中
Jack, across the hall, through the kitchen.
杰克  穿过大厅  通过厨房
One agent at the door.
门口有名特工
Copy that.
收到
I'm in the elevator.
我在电梯里
Where are they concentrating their agents?
他们把特工都聚集到哪儿了?
Jack, they cut off access to my grid.
杰克  他们中止了我进入网格的权限
I don't know where the agents are.
我不知道特工都在哪
They were grouping in the lobby.
他们当时正在大厅里分组
I'm getting out on the second floor.
我从二层下电梯
Come on, Jack.
快点  杰克
What'd you get for me on Chevensky?
找到切文斯基了么?
He's not a passenger,
他不是乘客
he's a baggage supervisor at the airport.
他是一名机场安检员
Jack Bauer! Agent O'Brian!
杰克・鲍尔! 特工 欧布赖恩!
The perimeter is sealed! There is no way out!
你已经被包围了! 没有出路了!
Step into view with your hands in the air!
快出来投降吧!
We know you're down here!
我们知道你就在这儿!
Do not shoot!
别开枪!
We need them alive!
要活捉!
No one fire!
不许开枪!
Step out of the vehicle!
从车里出来!
Check the back!
从后面检查车厢!
Get the side!
站到旁边!
Step to your left!
向左走!
Get down on your knees!
跪下!
Cuff her!
铐起来!
Open the back!
打开后面!
Bauer's not here.
鲍尔不在这儿
Secure the area.
清理现场
Get in!
快进来!
Give me my bag!
把包给我!
Got it.
好了
- Frank. - Yeah, it's me.
- 弗兰克 - 喂 是我
Listen, Derek is all right.
听着 德里克没事
I just need to know where you are.
我需要知道你在哪里
I'm on the 210 at the 10.
我在210和10号公路的交汇处
Okay, I want you to take the 10
好的 我要里沿着10号公路
East to the Ontario Airport.
向东到达安大略机场
When you get there,
你到达那里时
I want you to go to the parking lot in front of the terminal.
我希望你把车停到候机厅前面的停车场
I'll meet you on the west side of that parking lot.
我会在停车场的西面跟你碰头
Do you understand me?
明白了吗?
Yeah, yeah.
是的
Diane, listen to me.
黛安 听我说
I am so sorry that I got you involved in this.
我很抱歉把你牵扯进来
But everything's gonna be all right.
但是一切都会没事的
I'll be there in a few minutes, okay?
我一会儿就到那里 好吗?
Okay.
好的
Okay. Thanks.
谢谢
Mr. Buchanan, this is Agent Jennings.
布坎南先生 我是詹宁斯探员
There's no sign of Jack Bauer yet,
没有杰克・鲍尔的踪迹
but we've apprehended your agent, Chloe O'Brian.
但是我们抓到了你的探员科洛依・奥布赖恩
She was trying to escape our agents
她试图躲避我们的探员
and get away from the building.
从大楼里逃走
You're telling me she wasn't under duress?
你是在说 她没有被挟持?
Not as far as I can tell.
应该没有
Put her on the phone.
让他听电话
Uncuff her.
解开她的手铐
Bill Buchanan wants to talk to you.
比尔・布坎南要跟你说话
Hi.
头
Chloe, what the hell's going on?
科洛依 到底发生了什么事?
Jack didn't kill anybody.
杰克没有杀人
He's being framed to cover up
他们陷害他来掩盖
the real reason Palmer was assassinated.
帕默被暗杀的真正原因
This is according to Jack.
这是杰克说的?
This is according to the man who killed Palmer.
这是杀害帕默的那个人说的
I heard his dying confession.
我听到了他临死前的口供
You'll find his body at the refinery,
你们能在石油加工厂找到他的尸体
just north of the city, at Variel and Topanga.
就在城北 威芮尔和托品家附近
Chloe, do you have evidence that Palmer's assassination
科洛依 你是否有证据
has anything to do with the Summit?
表明帕默遇刺与即将到来高峰会有关?
No
没有
No. Jack's trying to figure all that out.
杰克正在试图查出来
How? Where is he?
怎么查? 他在哪里?
I can't tell you.
我不能告诉你
Why not?
为什么不能?
Because I don't think you believe him.
因为我认为你不信任他
I think you're just trying to arrest him.
我认为你只是想要逮捕他
Chloe, I'm not going to ask you again.
科洛依 我不会再问你第二遍了
I'm ordering you to tell me where Jack is.
我命令你告诉我 杰克在哪里
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I'd like to tell you, but I can't.
我也很想告诉你 但是我不能
Chloe!
科洛依!
Sir?
先生
Bring her back to CTU.
把她带回CTU
Curtis, take a team to the refinery.
柯蒂斯 带一组人去石油加工厂
See what you can find there.
去那里看看能发现什么
Edgar, make sure Chloe goes into a holding cell
埃德加 等科洛依回来后
when she gets back.
把她关到拘留室里
That woman, Chloe...
那个女的 科洛依...
she told me some stuff about what you used to do.
她告诉我一些关于你以前做的事情
Yeah, well, she shouldn't have.
哦 她不该告诉你的
Why did you have to lie?
你什么必须要说谎?
Couldn't you have just told us the truth?
你就不能告诉我们真相吗?
First of all, Derek,
首先 德里克
you have to understand that I never thought anything
你必须明白我从没想到
like this could ever happen.
会发生这样的事情
After your mother rented me that room,
在你母亲把那个房间租给我之后
I started to remember what it was like to have a family.
我开始记起有一个家庭是什么感觉
How nice it was.
那真是太美好了
I started to believe that a guy
我开始相信
like me could actually get a second chance.
像我这样的人还能够再得到一次人生机会
I know you don't believe this now...
我知道你现在不会相信这些话...
but I really do care about you.
但是我真的很在乎你
And I care about your mother.
我也在乎你的母亲
I hope, one day, you can understand that.
我希望 有一天 你能明白这些
Charles?
查尔斯?
Evelyn said you wanted to talk to me?
伊夫林说你想跟我谈谈?
I do.
是的
Did Walt find the tape of the phone call?
沃尔特找到那盘电话录音了?
I told him approximately when it took place.
我告诉了他事情发生的大概时间了
Why don't we sit down?
我们为什么不坐下来?
No. I don't want to sit down.
不 我不想坐下来
All right.
好吧
You don't need to be concerned that there's any
你不需要去关心
connection between David's death and the phone call
大卫的死跟他打给你的电话
that he made to you.
有什么关系
He said it was a matter of national security.
他说这事关国家安全
Those were his exact words.
这些就是他的原话
There's got to be a connection, of course.
这当中当然有联系
There isn't.
没有
David was killed by an unstable ex-CTU agent.
大卫是被一个不可靠的前CTU探员杀害的
This was not a conspiracy.
这不是一起阴谋事件
This was one man acting out of some kind of grudge.
这只是一个人实施的报复行动
Did you hear the call?
你听了那个电话了吗?
Marty, can we just drop this?
马蒂 我们就不要谈这个了好吗?
Did you or didn't you hear it?!
你听了没有?!
Martha, it's David Palmer.
玛莎 我是大卫・帕默
Did I wake you?
我把你吵醒了吗?
No, no, David, not at all.
没有 大卫 没有
What's going on?
发生什么事情了?
I need to talk to you.
我需要跟你谈谈
It's hardly a matter of national security,
这说不上是什么有关国家安全的事
but I'm hosting a charity dinner next month
但是 下个月我要办一个慈善晚宴
for the Art in Action Scholarship Program.
是为"艺术行动"奖学金项目办的
No. That's not what he said.
不 他不是这样说的
No. That's not it.
我非常希望你
I would very much like you and the president to be there...
和总统能够出席
No. That is not it. That is not it, Charles.
不 不是这样的 查尔斯
That's not it.
不是这样的
Let me...
让我...
Martha, listen!
玛莎 听着!
- Thank you, Martha. - Of course.
- 谢谢 玛莎  - 当然
Please send the president my best.
请向总统转达我的问候
That's not what he said.
不，不是这个...他不是这样说的
Yes, it is.
就是这个
No, that is... that is a trick.
不 这是...这是个骗局
Listen to me...
听我说...
-I am not crazy.
我没有发疯
- Marty... Martha! - I know what I heard!
- 马蒂...玛莎! 听我说  - 我清楚我听到了什么
I know what I heard.
我清楚我听到了什么
I spoke to Dr. Hill.
我跟希尔医生谈过了
He said if you were not consistent
他说 如果你不接受药物治疗的话
with your medication, you could become disoriented.
你会变得精神错乱的
Your memory can be affected.
你的记忆会受影响
He said that?
他这么说的?
Yes!
是的!
That's why you remember something different.
所以你会记错一些事情
I know you don't like how these pills make you feel,
我明白你不喜欢那些药片给你带来的反应
but you need to take them.
但是你必须吃药
If Jack was responsible for President Palmer's assassination,
如果杰克要为帕默遇刺负责的话
why would Chloe cover for him?
科洛依为什么要掩护他?
It just doesn't make sense.
这说不通
There's something else going on here,
一定还发生了其他的事情
and we're missing it.
我们还没查到
NSA just intercepted some chatter
国家安全局刚刚截获了一条消息
identifying the summit as a target.
表明此次高峰会是某个行动的袭击目标
We're sourcing it now,
我们正在追踪来源
but the reliability is approaching 95%.
但是可靠性是接近95%
Is there a timeframe?
有时间表吗?
Within the next 15 minutes.
在15分钟之内
That's when the Russian President is scheduled to land.
那就是俄罗斯总统预定到达的时间
President Logan said he will not postpone this summit.
洛根总统说他不会推迟会见
In light of this, he may not have a choice.
根据这个情况 他也许没有其他选择了
Put me through to Mike Novick.
帮我接麦克・诺维克
I'm watching Suvarov's helicopter leave the airbase.
我在监视苏沃洛夫的直升机飞离空军基地
His arrival at the retreat is on schedule.
他会按计划到达戴维营
As are we.
我们也是
We'll go dark now.
我们要中断通讯了
No communication until after you strike.
在你们发动袭击之前不再通话
I will monitor your progress from here.
我会在这里监视你们的行动
Understood.
明白
I'll touch you.
再联系你
Mr. President?
总统先生
Yeah, Mike, what is it?
麦克 什么事?
CTU has confirmed intelligence suggesting
CTU确认有情报显示
President Suvarov's helicopter will be targeted.
苏沃洛夫总统的直升机会成为袭击目标
How good is this intelligence?
这个情报有多可靠?
Very good.
很可靠
They're updating their recommendation
他们更新了他们的报告
that you delay or reschedule.
建议您推迟或者重新安排日期
No.
不
I've told them, I'm telling you.
我已经告诉过他们 现在我告诉你：
I will not postpone this summit!
我不会推迟这次高峰会
Then at least, have Suvarov alter his arrival plan.
那么至少让苏沃洛夫修改他的抵达计划
His chopper can land at a different site
他的直升机可以在另外一个地点降落
and he can be brought here by motorcade.
然后由护卫车队接他过来
The risk would be substantially reduced.
危险性就会大大降低了
And the impact of his arrival would also be reduced.
那他抵达这里的影响也会降低了
I've got the media waiting
我已经让媒体在这里等待
for a landing five minutes from now!
5分钟之后他会抵达
Mr. President...
总统先生...
I don't want to hear it, Walt.
我不想听这些沃尔特
It's up to Secret Service and the Air Force
保护我们的领空
to protect our airspace!
是特工和空军的责任!
Make sure they do the job.
要让他们尽责
There's your mom.
你妈妈来了
Hey.
嘿
I'm sorry about the way I treated you earlier.
很抱歉我之前骗了你
You're a good kid.
你是个好孩子
Go get your mom.
去找你妈妈吧
Mom?!
妈妈?!
Oh, my God!
噢 老天!
Oh, are you okay?
你还好么?
I was so worried!
知道我有多担心你么!
I'm sorry.
抱歉让你担心了
You got to tell me right now
你现在就得告诉我
what the hell is going on here, Frank.
这到底是怎么回事  弗兰克
My name's not Frank.
我不叫弗兰克
It's Jack Bauer.
我叫杰克・鲍尔
I lied to you.
我向你撒谎了
I lied to you about a lot of things.
我隐瞒了好多事情
I'll explain as soon as I can,
我会尽快向你解释的
but right now, you and Derek need to go to this address.
但现在  你和德里克必须去这个地址
CTU?
CTU?
Counterterrorist Unit.
反恐小组
I used to work there.
我曾在那里工作过
You need to ask for a man named Bill Buchanan.
你去那里找个叫比尔・布坎南的人
Tell him I sent you.
告诉他是我叫你们去的
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I have to go.
必须得走了
When we get there, what do we tell him?
到了那儿  我们该说些什么?
Tell him the truth.
如实告诉他就行
Where can I find the Baggage Claim Supervisor?
在哪能找到安检部门的主管?
Down that hall to the left.
大厅尽头向左拐
Thank you.
多谢
DOD is still giving us the all clear
国防部的情报还是显示
on the air space and the retreat.
领空和戴维营都没有情况
Any word from our agents on the ground?
地勤人员那边有消息么?
Okay.
好的
I'm all quiet so far.
到现在为止还没有任何动静
But if they're going to attack the helicopter,
他们要想攻击直升机的话
it's going to be now.
现在已经下手了
- Hi, Mr. President... - It's a pleasure to see you.
- 你好  总统先生  - 很荣幸见到您
Our intel must have been wrong.
我们的消息可能有误
Mom, do you see those men?
妈  看到那些人了么?
Yeah.
是的
That's where Jack went.
那就是杰克要找的人
Something's wrong.
有些不对劲
I have to warn Jack.
我得去告诉杰克
Derek, where are you going?
德里克  你要去哪儿?
Come back here!
快回来!
Derek! Come back here!
德里克 !快回来!
Derek!
德里克!
Come back here!
快回来!
- Wait! - I have to get my son.
- 等一下!  - 我要去找我的儿子!
No, you can't! You can't!
不! 你快回去! 你不能...
Please move your car !
请把您的车移走
I've got to get my son.
我要找我的儿子
Derek!
德里克!
Get back in!
快回去!
Why was President Palmer killed?!
帕默总统为什么被杀?!
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
You are going to tell me what I want to know.
你必须告诉我所有我想知道的
It's just a question of how much you want it to hurt.
这将决定你将要忍受的疼痛程度
No!
不!
Quiet!
都闭嘴
You will not be harmed as long as
你们不会受到伤害的
your president complies with our wishes.
只要你们的总统答应我们的条件
Derek!
德里克!
Ma'am, stop!
女士  不要过去!
My son is in danger
我儿子有危险!
I have to get my son!
我要去找我的儿子!
I have dealt with the Martha Logan situation.
玛莎・洛根那边我已经安排好了
She's not going to be a problem?
不会有什么问题吧?
No.
不会
I was able to alter the tape of the phone call
电话录音我已经做过手脚了
before the President heard it.
在总统听见之前
There's no longer any evidence on my end that
再也不会有什么证据了
Palmer was trying to warn her about the attack.
那些关于帕默试图警告她关于攻击的事情
Good.
很好
The terminal and the hostages are secure.
终端和人质都很安全
It'll only be a matter of time
现在需要的只是等待
until the president is notified of the demands.
直到他收到我们的要求